<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>All Posts - AB Engineering Blog</title>
        <link>https://blog.alphabravo.io/posts/</link>
        <description>All Posts | AB Engineering Blog</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 11:00:00 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.alphabravo.io/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Powerful Single Node K3s on Hetzner for CHEAP!</title>
    <link>https://blog.alphabravo.io/posts/2021/single-node-rke2-pt1/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 11:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.alphabravo.io/posts/2021/single-node-rke2-pt1/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/assets/single-node-k3s-full.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>The K3s Cluster No, your eyes do not deceive you. This is a very similarly named blog to our Powerful Single Node RKE2 on Hetzner for CHEAP! (Part 1).
Some folks don&rsquo;t want to deploy RKE2, and we don&rsquo;t want you to feel left out. In this blog we are going to deploy K3s in place of RKE2.
If you want to see why we chose Hetzner for this specific deployment, go check out the previous blog.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Powerful Single Node RKE2 on Hetzner for CHEAP! (Part 1)</title>
    <link>https://blog.alphabravo.io/posts/2021/single-node-rke2-pt1/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 13:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.alphabravo.io/posts/2021/single-node-rke2-pt1/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/assets/single-node-rke2-full.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>The RKE2 Cluster In this blog, we will explain how to deploy a powerful, single node RKE2 cluster on Hetzner. It will provide the following resources.
 Single Node RKE2 Kubernetes Cluster NGINX Ingress into your cluster Rancher Multi Cluster Manager Web UI to manage your cluster  Why Hetzner? Want an easy, powerful, single node, publically accessible Kubernetes cluster? Well, do we have a deal for you! (said in my best Billy Mays voice.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Why We Chose Nifi Over Databrew</title>
    <link>https://blog.alphabravo.io/posts/2021/why-we-chose-nifi-over-databrew/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 13:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.alphabravo.io/posts/2021/why-we-chose-nifi-over-databrew/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/assets/apache-nifi-full.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>Why AlphaBravo Chose Nifi Over Databrew Recently, the AlphaBravo engineering team began working on a new product we’re calling ABScan. Our goal is to provide a platform which uses multiple scanning utilities via a single interface.
Early on in our development process, we realized that we would need to take multiple JSON outputs, convert them into CSV and SQL, and merge the results. This would require the use of an ETL to automate the transformation of the data generated so we could create CSV files for reports and SQL data for long term storage.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Rancher Multi-Cluster Management UI</title>
    <link>https://blog.alphabravo.io/posts/2021/rancher-multi-cluster-management-ui/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 13:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.alphabravo.io/posts/2021/rancher-multi-cluster-management-ui/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/assets/rancher-ui-full.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>What is Rancher Multi-Cluster Management If you have ventured into container management and Kubernetes for your organization (or even for yourself), you have quickly realized that you need a robust way to manage more than one cluster easily. In fact, you probably want an easier way to manage a single cluster.
The official Kubernetes dashboard is&hellip; sub-optimal. There are a few other open-source options out there, but they lack in many areas.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Why We Use Rancher</title>
    <link>https://blog.alphabravo.io/posts/2021/why-we-use-rancher/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 11:35:58 &#43;0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.alphabravo.io/posts/2021/why-we-use-rancher/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/assets/ab-uses-rancher-full.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>Why We Use Rancher Ok, let&rsquo;s get this out of the way. Yes, we are a Rancher Gold Partner and yes, we provide Rancher Training.
We are not those things because we are corpo shills. We partnered with Rancher because we use their products anyway.
  We use them in production (RKE2 and K3s).
  We use them on our Raspberry Pi clusters (K3s).
  We use them in Docker (K3d)]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Welcome To The Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.alphabravo.io/posts/2021/welcome-to-the-blog/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 10:35:58 &#43;0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.alphabravo.io/posts/2021/welcome-to-the-blog/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/assets/welcome-full1.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>Welcome To The Blog We are excited to have you here.
As technology enthusiasts with a broad range of experiences, we hope to convey some tales, some tech, and some thoughts around the current state of DevSecOps.
Our focus is mainly on building robust platforms using open-source software. But don&rsquo;t be confused if we talk about non-open source software too. We are a small team and we understand very well that sometimes you need a product or tool that &ldquo;just works&rdquo;.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
